{
  "user": [
    {
      "id": "b60db27-6f7-bb0-cdc6-7d4dea042ff8",
      "email": "admin@gmail.com",
      "password": "mohit",
      "cpassword": "mohit"
    },
    {
      "id": "e7a254-a03f-22ec-e02f-53fcac5348",
      "email": "admin2@gmail.com",
      "password": "mohit",
      "cpassword": "mohit"
    },
    {
      "id": "ffdc1ec-7c45-735-3827-e36b37e18",
      "email": "admin1@gmail.com",
      "password": "mohit",
      "cpassword": "mohit"
    }
  ],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "0353c3-dc44-d06-61ff-268ecdf53d",
      "userId": "e7a254-a03f-22ec-e02f-53fcac5348",
      "mcq": {
        "question": "How can you create an e-mail link?",
        "option1": "<mail href=\"a@b\">",
        "option2": "<mail>a@b</mail>",
        "option3": "<a href=\"a@b\">",
        "option4": "<a href=\"mailto:a@b.com\">",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      "msq": {
        "question": "Which of the following JavaScript cannot do?",
        "option1": " JavaScript can react to events",
        "option2": "JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements",
        "option3": "JavaScript can be use to validate data",
        "option4": "javascript use in designing also",
        "answer": [
          "A",
          "B",
          "C"
        ]
      },
      "trueFalse": {
        "question": "Easy data exchange great about XML!",
        "answer": "True"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "d1e1131-5fe6-e14-1eb-8ee1faf2116e",
      "userId": "ffdc1ec-7c45-735-3827-e36b37e18",
      "mcq": {
        "question": "what is js?",
        "option1": "html",
        "option2": "css",
        "option3": "js",
        "option4": "python",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      "msq": {
        "question": "what is ml?",
        "option1": "scss",
        "option2": "sss",
        "option3": "sdadsa",
        "option4": "dsasds",
        "answer": [
          "B",
          "A",
          "C"
        ]
      },
      "trueFalse": {
        "question": "is this a mobile?",
        "answer": ""
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "8e1a5a-b22d-018-bf8-f26f13846fe3",
      "userId": "ffdc1ec-7c45-735-3827-e36b37e18",
      "mcq": {
        "question": "htmlo?",
        "option1": "dwwdwd",
        "option2": "wdwd",
        "option3": "wdqwd",
        "option4": "dwqwdqdwqw",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      "msq": {
        "question": "wwwwwwwwwwwwwww",
        "option1": "wwwwwwwwwww",
        "option2": "sadsdsda",
        "option3": "dasdsa",
        "option4": "sdadsds",
        "answer": [
          "B",
          "A"
        ]
      },
      "trueFalse": {
        "question": "sddssddsa",
        "answer": "False"
      }
    },
    {
      "id": "44bb08b-2b20-843c-66c4-fe35e146ebf",
      "userId": "b60db27-6f7-bb0-cdc6-7d4dea042ff8",
      "mcq": {
        "question": "what is js?",
        "option1": "html",
        "option2": "css",
        "option3": "javascript",
        "option4": "python",
        "answer": "C"
      },
      "msq": {
        "question": "what is ml?",
        "option1": "ai",
        "option2": "python",
        "option3": "machine",
        "option4": "robot",
        "answer": [
          "A",
          "C"
        ]
      },
      "trueFalse": {
        "question": "is this a mobile?",
        "answer": "False"
      }
    }
  ],
  "answers": [
    {
      "questioId": "d1e1131-5fe6-e14-1eb-8ee1faf2116e",
      "id": "2ccf56f-8841-3b41-d853-2713aa73cc8d",
      "user": "mohit",
      "mcqAnswer": "C",
      "msqAnswer": [
        "B",
        "A"
      ],
      "trueFalseAnswer": "True"
    },
    {
      "questioId": "44bb08b-2b20-843c-66c4-fe35e146ebf",
      "id": "2ef7f5-d86-f8c-1bfb-7a621720bbdb",
      "user": "mohit",
      "mcqAnswer": "C",
      "msqAnswer": [
        "C",
        "B"
      ],
      "trueFalseAnswer": "True"
    }
  ]
}